Friendship has no last call.
The Greatest Beer Run Ever is a drama, comedy, war
film directed by Peter Farrelly.
Chickie wants to support his friends fighting in Vietnam, so he does
something wild—personally bring them American beer.
What starts as a well-meaning journey quickly
changes Chickie's life and perspective.
John 'Chickie' Donohue, played by Zac Efron.
Arthur Coates, played by Russell Crowe.
Bobby Pappas, played by Kyle Allen.
The Colonel, played by Bill Murray.
Rick Duggan, played by Jake Picking.
Kevin McLoone, played by Will Ropp.
The Greatest Beer Run Ever is a 2022 American biographical war comedy drama film, co-written and directed by
Peter Farrelly, based on the book of the same name by John "Chickie" Donohue and Joanna Molloy.
The film, starring Zac Efron and Russell Crowe, follows the true story of Donohue, who, as a young man,
sneaks into the Vietnam War to deliver some beer to his friends while they serve their duty.
The Greatest Beer Run Ever had its world premiere at the 2022 Toronto International Film Festival on September 13, 2022,
and released in select US theaters on September 23 and on Apple TV+ on September 30, 2022, by Apple Studios.
The film received mixed-to-negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, based on novel or book,
war correspondent, beer, based on true story.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.